truecredit.com 2017-12-13

# Understand Your Credit Report | TrueCredit

##  Security 

TrueCredit understands the confidentiality of information contained in credit reports, and we safeguard the privacy of all information you provide to this Web Site. 

###  Identity Verification (IV) 

TrueCredit has designed an Identity Verification System in order to protect your security and privacy. IV seeks to confirm that your personal credit report is being viewed by YOU. 

When a customer requests a credit report, IV is intended to confirm the customer's identity. If you cannot provide the correct information, the system does not allow you to view the report. (Please Note: If you are currently in the identity verification process and you need help, please contact our Customer Service Team). 

###  SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) Encryption 

To ensure that your credit information remains secure and confidential, TrueCredit uses programs that encrypt the data you provide on the order form before transmission to TrueCredit. 

Encryption is a way of coding the information in a file so that, if it is intercepted by a third party as it travels over a network, it cannot be read. Only the person or persons that have the right type of decoding software can unscramble the message. Thus, your encrypted information can only be read by TrueCredit. 

* * *

##  TrueCredit Privacy Statement 

TrueCredit is firmly committed to respecting the consumer's right to privacy and has created this Privacy Statement to demonstrate our commitment. 

Last updated August 12, 2013 

###  The Information We Collect from You 

TrueCredit allows you to access the TrueCredit product through our Web site. We collect your personal information only if you decide to purchase TrueCredit, subscribe to our newsletter, or surveys or transact other business with us. In order to process your transactions and provide you with quality customer service, we need your full name and current and/or billing address, your email address (so we can contact you) and, if you purchase one of our products, a valid credit card number, your Social Security number and certain other personal information, such as your date of birth, address information, employment information, and certain credit card and loan account information. We use personal information to authenticate the credit card number and to confirm that the person requesting your credit report as part of TrueCredit really is you and not an impostor or other person improperly seeking to access your information. 

###  What Security Measures We Take 

TrueCredit takes precautions to secure your personal information. If and when we ask you to provide your personal information, we will do so through a Web page that uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. This protocol provides security for your information by encrypting it as it travels from your computer to our computer. We then move all of the personal information that we collect or obtain about you, including your credit report, to a special computer for security purposes by means of a one-way transfer on our proprietary network. This special computer is not connected to the Internet, and TrueCredit has controls in place to limit access to and secure the data maintained therein. 

###  How We Use and Share Your Personal Information 

If you indicate to us that you are interested in receiving information regarding other products and services from TrueCredit and third party partners, your name, e-mail address and other registration information may be shared with a third party in order to present these offers to you. Personal information that is shared with these entities will be monitored in accordance with our security and confidentiality policies. If you prefer not to receive such information, you may indicate your preference by marking the appropriate box when you register, place an order or update your account information, and TrueCredit will not send you any promotional materials. 

###  Emails 

When you order TrueCredit, we will email you a receipt of your purchase. The TrueCredit product also includes alert emails that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly basis. These emails are part of the TrueCredit benefits and cannot be disabled for persons who are TrueCredit members. 

###  Ordering 

When you order TrueCredit or other product or service, TrueCredit must share some of your personal information with third parties in order to process your transaction. For example, TrueCredit must share your name, address and social security number with one or more of the major credit reporting agencies in order to obtain your requested credit reports, and must share your name, address and credit card account number with our credit card processing partner in order to process your payment. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

###  Third Parties 

If you indicated to us when you registered, placed an order or updated your account that you were interested in receiving information about products and services provided by TrueCredit, and its third party marketing partners your name, email address and other registration information may be shared with a third party in order to present these offers to you. These entities are only allowed to use shared information for the intended purpose only and will be monitored in accordance with our security and confidentiality policies. In the event you indicate that you want to receive personalized offers from TrueCredit based on information from your credit profile, your credit information may be used to serve relevant ads to you when you visit the site and provide other relevant offers from TrueCredit based on such information. TrueCredit also may disclose your personal information to third parties in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with, or be responsive to, legal process served on us (such as a subpoena), or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of TrueCredit, our users or others. In addition, we may disclose your personal information to consultants, agents and advisors, such as attorneys and accountants, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is within the scope of their professional duties to TrueCredit and with the understanding that such professionals will abide by our security and confidentiality policies. In the event that you unsubscribe from email communications, we may share your email address with our compliance agents or approved marketing partners to prevent you from receiving additional offers. 

###  The Collection of Anonymous Data 

In order to enhance the usefulness of our Web site and our products and services, TrueCredit will collect data about our customers' use of our Web site, in a manner that does not include any personally identifiable information. While you browse the TrueCredit Web site, we note which pages of our site you visit and note the IP address of your computer (as all Web sites do automatically), but we do not link that address information to your personal information for marketing purposes but may for the purpose of product delivery. The general information we gather enables us to serve our customers better by continually enhancing our site based on up-to-date use patterns. 

###  Information Regarding Your Subscription 

We may use information about your TrueCredit subscription, such as your usage patterns, to customize your web site and/or customer service experience. 

###  Updating Your Personal Information and Email Preferences 

TrueCredit is not responsible for and cannot amend the information in your credit report, which is produced by one or more credit reporting agencies. If you believe that some of the information in your credit report is inaccurate, you must contact the applicable credit reporting agency directly. 

###  Notification of Changes to this Privacy Statement 

TrueCredit may amend this Privacy Statement at any time, and without advance notice. We recommend that from time to time you review this Privacy Statement to check for changes. 

###  Possible Acquisition 

In the event of an acquisition of all or part of TrueCredit by another company, or in the event that TrueCredit were to sell or dispose of all or a part of the business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by the TrueCredit business, which could include your personal information, subject to applicable law. The acquirer's privacy policy might be different than TrueCredit's privacy policy, or the acquirer might choose to amend TrueCredit's privacy policy. You will be notified by email if, as a result of such acquisition, TrueCredit's privacy policy is materially changed or if the acquirer's privacy policy is materially different than TrueCredit's privacy policy. In connection with such notice, you will be given an opportunity to inform the acquirer that you do not consent to the use or disclosure by the acquirer of your personal information in accordance with such new or revised privacy policy. 

If you would like at any time to review our then-current Privacy Statement, please visit http://www.TrueCredit.com/privacy

###  The Use of Cookies 

TrueCredit uses "cookies," which are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes, to facilitate your access to our products and services. TrueCredit uses cookies in accordance with industry-standard protocols, and does not use cookies, either directly or in conjunction with other Web sites, to track your movement to Web sites other than TrueCredit. If you would like more information about cookies, you can visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/n_cookie_faq.htm>. TrueCredit uses two different types of cookies. One type of cookie is used so that our site "recognizes" you each time you return using the same computer, and you do not have to re-enter all your personal information on each visit. You can set your Web browser to refuse to accept this cookie, or delete this type of cookie from your hard drive, and still access our products and services, as long as you re-enter information each time you visit. The second type of cookie is needed so that we can process each step of your transactions with us. If you refuse to accept this type of cookie, you will not be able to access our products and services. Most Web browsers automatically delete this type of cookie when you terminate your session. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site or on other sites which we use for advertising. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness; and they are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

###  Links to Other Web Sites 

Some pages on the TrueCredit Web site may contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

###  Policy Regarding Children 

We define children as individuals under the age of 16. Our Web Site is not intended for the use of children and we do not intend to collect information about children through our Web Site. You must be at least 18 to access any products through this website or to join TrueCredit as a member entitled to membership benefits. 

###  TrueCredit 

TrueCredit is a trade name of TransUnion Interactive, Inc., a Delaware corporation based in San Luis Obispo, California. 

* * *

##  Site Terms of Use Agreement 

Welcome to the web site, www.TrueCredit.com, (the "Site"). This Terms of Use Agreement ("Agreement") contains the terms and conditions upon which you ("you," or the "member") may use the Site or access TrueCredit or any products through the Site. You agree to be legally bound by these terms. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this Site. 

The terms and conditions that specifically apply to the TrueCredit product are in addition to these Site Terms of use. These Site Terms of use do not override the TrueCredit Product Agreement. 

###  General Terms 

TrueCredit maintains this Site to provide you with information about the TrueCredit product and to deliver TrueCredit to Members. From time to time we may revise these terms and conditions. Revisions will be effective when posted or as otherwise stated. 

TransUnion, LLC ("TransUnion"), TransUnion Interactive and TrueCredit are not credit repair organizations, or similarly regulated organizations under other applicable laws, and do not provide credit repair advice. 

TransUnion, TransUnion Interactive and TrueCredit's credit monitoring offerings monitor only the credit file associated with the purchasing consumer, and do not monitor, compare or cross-reference the credit file associated with the purchasing consumer to any other credit file(s) maintained by the applicable credit bureau(s). 

The images, text, screens, web pages, materials, data, content and other information ("Content") used and displayed on the Site, including, but not limited to, TransUnion Interactive™, TransUnion Interactive™ and Design, TrueCredit™, TrueCredit and Design™, TrueCredit™, TrueCredit™ and Design, are the property of TrueCredit or its licensors and are protected by copyright, trademark and other laws. In addition to our rights in individual elements of the Content within the Site, TrueCredit owns copyright or patent rights in the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of such Content. You may copy the Content from the Site for your personal or educational use only, provided that each copy includes any copyright, trademark or service mark notice or attribution as they appear on the pages copied. Except as provided in the preceding sentence, none of the Content may be copied, displayed, distributed, downloaded, licensed, modified, published, reposted, reproduced, reused, sold, transmitted, used to create a derivative work or otherwise used for public or commercial purposes without the express written permission of TrueCredit or the owner of the Content. 

###  Disclaimer of Warranties and Liabilities 

OUR SITE, INCLUDING ALL CONTENT, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH THIS SITE, IS PROVIDED TO YOU "AS IS". TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER TRUECREDIT NOR ITS AFFILIATES MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER AS TO THE CONTENT, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH OUR SITE, THAT A USER WILL HAVE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO OUR SITE, CONTENT, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OR THAT OUR SITE, CONTENT, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WILL BE ERROR-FREE. IN ADDITION, TRUECREDIT AND ITS AFFILIATES AND SUPPLIERS DISCLAIM ALL EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON INFRINGEMENT AND INFORMATIONAL CONTENT. THEREFORE, YOU AGREE THAT YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR SITE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND CONTENT ARE AT YOUR OWN RISK. BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT NEITHER TRUECREDIT NOR ITS AFFILIATES AND SUPPLIERS HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU (WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE) FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR SPECIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SITE, CONTENT, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES (EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), INCLUDING LIABILITY ASSOCIATED WITH ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT. 

###  Registration and Accurate Information 

If you decide to register on our Site, or purchase our products or services you may be required to register, provide personal information, and select a user name and password. You agree to provide accurate information in your registration and not to share your password with third parties. You agree not to impersonate another person or to select or use a user name or password of another person. You agree to notify TrueCredit promptly of any unauthorized use of your account and of any loss, theft or disclosure of your password. Failure to comply with these requirements shall constitute a breach of these terms and conditions and shall constitute grounds for immediate termination of your account and your right to use the Site. 

###  Our Privacy Policy 

We define children as individuals under the age of 16. Our Web Site is not intended for the use of children and we do not intend to collect information about children through our Web Site. You must be at least 18 to access any products through this website or to join TrueCredit as a member entitled to membership benefits. 

###  Notices 

You should send any notices or other communications regarding our Site, products or services to TrueCredit, 100 Cross Street, Suite 202, San Luis Obispo, CA 93401. 

TrueCredit is a trade name of TransUnion Interactive, Inc., a Delaware corporation based in San Luis Obispo, California. 

###  Applicable Law 

The laws applicable to the interpretation of these terms and conditions shall be the laws of the State of Delaware, USA, and applicable federal law, without regard to any conflict of law provisions. TrueCredit can provide credit reports only for individuals who have established credit in the United States. Those who choose to access this Site from outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws. You agree that any and all disputes arising under this Agreement, if submitted to a court of law, shall be submitted to the state and federal courts of New Castle County, Delaware, USA.
